[Music]
Madam, you have got ₹100.  Hey brother, what are you asking for
₹100 for?  Are you selling Pani Puri or
gold and silver?  Hey madam, it will cost only ₹100.
Brother, I will not be able to give
so much money.  Brother, please feed me Pani Puri.  Hey
brother, don't eat their Pani Puri.  Why?  There is a
cockroach in their pani puri.  Hey brother, I am
not eating Pani Puri.  I am going.
Brother, please feed me Pani Puri.  Yes.
Chotu, what happened?  Why didn't that madam eat Pani Puri
?  Looks like he owns it.
Hey brother, there was a cockroach in your pani puri.  Did
you see a cockroach with your own eyes
?  Yes, I saw it with my own eyes.
Why?  You had said that the stick had fallen in the water.
[music]
[applause] come
on